

# Babulal

SENIOR Graphic Designer



https://www.behance.net/varunsurya



https://www.linkedin.com/in/babu-lal-0b1033185/



https://instagram.com/varunsurya\_arts?igshid=NGExMmI2YTkyZg==

## ABOUT ME

Able to create an effective and innovative design to convey desired ideas. Experience working with clients to identify needs and present solutions. Collaborating with the marketing, sales, and product development department.

Driven with a strong work ethic.

- © +91 8375 8473 00
- designervarunv@gmail.com
- 16/932, H Bapa Nagar, Pyare lal Road Karol Bagh, Delhi-110005

## LANGUAGE

- Hindi
- English

## SKILLS

ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR

ADOBE PHOTOSHOP

PREMIER PRO

AFTER EFFECT

3D max

## EDUCATION

Pursuing ANIMATION (Prime) from Arena Animation, Delhi

Degree / Bachelor of Arts Delhi University

Higher Secondary of C.B.S.E. from Govt Boys Sr. Secondary School Ramjas Lane 1

### EXPERIENCE



## Graphic Designer / Video Editor

RD MARKETING | DEC 2021- PRESENT

1+ Year experience in RD MARKETING as a Graphic Designer and video editor Situated at Karol Bagh Delhi

## Graphic Designer / Video Editor

NM DIGITAL ZONE | APR 2020- NOV 2021

1.5 Year experience in NM DIGITAL ZONE as a Graphic Designer Situated at Pitampura Delhi

## Graphic Designer

HARINI ADVERTISING | APR 2019- MAR 2020

1 Year experience in HARINI ADVERTISING as a Graphic Designer Situated at Pitampura Delhi

## INTEREST



- Sketching
- Listening Music
- Photography
- Socializing with people, listening their good and bad experiences and learning from the same